boatsandoutboards.co.uk 2017-09-29

# Privacy Policy | Boats and Outboards

**About Boatsandoutboards.co.uk**

Boatsandoutboards is an online community for all boat lovers. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of Boatsandoutboards's policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information you submit to us through our Website.

To provide a richer user experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network of friends. Boatsandoutboards members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them.

Boatsandoutboards.co.uk cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at privacy@boatsandoutboards.co.uk

**Information Collection and Use**

Boatsandoutboards.co.uk collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Boatsandoutboards.co.uk service. Boatsandoutboards.co.uk also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other.

Boatsandoutboards.co.uk also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the Boatsandoutboards.co.uk community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Boatsandoutboards, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network Users within a personal network communicate on Boatsandoutboards.co.uk with each other through the Boatsandoutboards.co.uk service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Boatsandoutboards.co.uk allows users to search for other members using first and last name, nickname and email addresses.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service.

**Third Party Advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Website. These companies may use Personal Information, such as gender or age, and other information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites, such as time of day of the login, IP address or information about the internet service provider (ISP), in order to provide advertisements on the Website about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members**

Boatsandoutboards members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our invitation system. Boatsandoutboards.co.uk stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations Boatsandoutboards.co.uk does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders. Recipients of invitations from Boatsandoutboards.co.uk may contact Boatsandoutboards.co.uk to request the removal of their information from our database.

**Cookies**

Boatsandoutboards.co.uk uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set - each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences - however, you must enable cookies from Boatsandoutboards.co.uk in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that Boatsandoutboards may allow 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Boatsandoutboards Privacy Policy.

**Forums, Boatsandoutboards and Diaries, Classifieds, Chat Rooms and Links**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Boatsandoutboards, Diaries, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications. Boatsandoutboards.co.uk contains links to sites. Boatsandoutboards.co.uk is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Boatsandoutboards.co.uk.

**Updating or Removing your Account Information**

Boatsandoutboards.co.uk users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as "Profile" and "Privacy".

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and third parties who we reasonably believe need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you and your Boatsandoutboards account information is protected by a password that you select. However, no company, including Boatsandoutboards, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Boatsandoutboards will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Boatsandoutboards.co.uk, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Boatsandoutboards.co.uk Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Boatsandoutboards reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Boatsandoutboards or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.

**Childrens' Privacy**

 Boatsandoutboards does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Boatsandoutboards Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Boatsandoutboards Sites at any time or in any manner. If Boatsandoutboards learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Boatsandoutboards Sites without verified parental consent, then Boatsandoutboards will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: privacy@Boatsandoutboards.co.uk
